https://www.fultonservices.com/privacy-policy/

Metro Atlanta’s Plumbing, Heating and Cooling Experts!
Only Fulton Services offers you unconditional service with a proven track record spanning 93 years.
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect? We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form. When completing web forms on our website, you may be asked for personal information. You can choose to visit our site anonymously by not responding to our requests for information. What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To process transactions
To send periodic emails
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
Your information, however public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by you. The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not, sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Third Party Links Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy. Changes to Our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on 1/17/2012.
Service Request
Name *
Phone Number*
Email *
Message*
Testimonials
They have always done a top-notch job. I’d use them and recommend them without question.
Jim F., Woodstock GA
Fulton is absolutely good. Their guys are very experienced and professional.
Susan J., Norcross GA
Fulton is a find. They got our air conditioner working in a hurry.
Bob Z., Atlanta GA
I’m a bit late with this review, but I wanted to once again express my thanks to you and Fulton for another job “well done” on my home. John and Stephen replaced our water line which fed from the county tap to our home. Here’s a short story I penned to describe the repair process, a bit tongue in cheek, and there might be a tiny amount of exaggeration…..
A Tale of Plumbing By-Pass Surgery
Part One- The Decision
It starts with a diagnosis from John Bauer… “Look son, the main … Read more
John D.
They are wonderful. We have used them for the last 11 years.
Walter A., Duluth GA
From the BlogFinding Ductwork Leaks in AtlantaSaving Money with a Programmable Thermostat in AtlantaCarbon Monoxide: The Silent, Invisible Killer in Atlanta, GAHorrifying Furnace Noises in Atlanta, GAHVAC Air Leak Testing & Sealing for Your Atlanta, GA Home
One Call or Click
Covers all  your plumbing or heating and cooling service needs – Fulton Plumbing is available 24/7 at (404) 602-0509.
Contact Us
Fulton Services
| 3565 Plant Atkinson Road
Building C | Atlanta, Georgia 30339 | (404) 602-0509
Fulton ServicesHomePlumbing ServicesDrain CleaningLeak DetectionFixture Repair & ReplacementRepiping & Pipe ReliningWater HeatersGas Line RepairTrenchless Sewer RepairPlumbing RemodelingBackflow PreventionStandby GeneratorsWater TreatmentSump PumpHeating ServicesHeating ProductsHeating RepairsHeating InstallationHeating MaintenanceIndoor Air QualityAir ConditioningCooling ProductsAir Conditioning RepairAir Conditioning InstallationAir Conditioning MaintenanceOur CompanyFulton Plumbing EmploymentCustomer CommentsAffiliations & CharitiesBlogContact UsPeace of Mind ProtectionRequest ServiceEnergy Savings AgreementsSpecialsCities We ServeFAQ
